Guide to the Time Inc. Subject Files 1889-2015 (bulk 1934-1993) MS 3009-RG 1
New-York Historical Society
- Series II: 1961 and Later, 1936-2015; 196504; 50 Linear feet (50 boxes)
  - Life Special Report: 1973 [RESTRICTED], 197282 (Offsite-box R5)
  - Life Special Reports: 1974-1975, 197281 (Offsite-box 473, Folder 14-15)
  - Life: 1974-1977, 197280 (Offsite-box 473)
  - Life: 1974-1977 [RESTRICTED], 197279 (Offsite-box R5)
  - Life: 1977: Edit: Banks Report, 197278 (Offsite-box 473, Folder 18)
  - Life: 1978: Publishing: Weekly Reports, 197277 (Offsite-box 473, Folder 20)
  - Life: 1978: Miscellaneous, 197276 (Offsite-box 474, Folder 1)
  - Life: 1978: Edit, 197275 (Offsite-box 474)
  - Life: 1978: Edit [RESTRICTED], 197274 (Offsite-box R5)
  - Life: 1978: Publishing: Miscellaneous, 197273 (Offsite-box 474, Folder 3-4)
  - Life: 1979: Miscellaneous, 197272 (Offsite-box 474, Folder 5)
  - Life: 1979: Edit, 197271 (Offsite-box 474)
  - Life: 1979: Edit [RESTRICTED], 197270 (Offsite-box R5)
  - Life: 1979: Publishing: Weekly Reports, 197269 (Offsite-box 474, Folder 8)
  - Life: 1979: Publishing: Miscellaneous, 197268 (Offsite-box 474, Folder 9)
  - Life: 1980: Edit: Miscellaneous, 197267 (Offsite-box 474, Folder 10)
  - Life: 1980: Publishing, 197266 (Offsite-box 474)
  - Life: 1980: Publishing [RESTRICTED], 197265 (Offsite-box R5)
  - Life: 1981: Edit: Miscellaneous, 197264 (Offsite-box 474)
  - Life: 1981: Edit: Miscellaneous [RESTRICTED], 197263 (Offsite-box R5)
  - Life: 1981: Publishing, 197262 (Offsite-box 474, Folder 13)
  - Life: 1982: Publishing, 197261 (Offsite-box 474, Folder 14)
  - Life: 1982: Edit, 197260 (Offsite-box 474, Folder 15)
  - Life: 1983: Edit, 197259 (Offsite-box 474, Folder 16)
  - Life: 1983: Publishing, 197258 (Offsite-box 474, Folder 17)
  - Life: 1984: Edit, 197257 (Offsite-box 474, Folder 18)
  - Life: 1984: Publishing, 197256 (Offsite-box 474, Folder 19)
  - Life: 1985: Edit: Miscellaneous, 197255 (Offsite-box 474, Folder 20)
  - Life: 1985: Publishing, 197254 (Offsite-box 474, Folder 21)
  - Life: 1986: Edit: Miscellaneous, 197253 (Offsite-box 474)
  - Life: 1986: Edit: Miscellaneous [RESTRICTED], 197252 (Offsite-box R5)
  - Life: 1986: Publishing, 197251 (Offsite-box 474, Folder 23)
  - Life: 1987: Edit, 197250 (Offsite-box 474, Folder 24)
  - Life: 1987: Publishing, 197249 (Offsite-box 474, Folder 25)
  - Life: 1988: Edit, 197248 (Offsite-box 474, Folder 26)
  - Life: 1988: Publishing, 197247 (Offsite-box 474, Folder 27)
  - Life: 1989: Edit, 197246 (Offsite-box 474, Folder 28)
  - Life: 1989: Publishing, 197245 (Offsite-box 474, Folder 29)
  - Life: 1990: Edit, 197244 (Offsite-box 475, Folder 1)
  - Life: 1990: Publishing, 197243 (Offsite-box 475, Folder 2)
  - Life: 1991: Edit, 197242 (Offsite-box 475, Folder 3)
  - Life: 1991: Edit: Special Weekly Issues: Persian Gulf War, 197241 (Offsite-box 475, Folder 4)
  - Life: 1991: Publishing, 197240 (Offsite-box 475, Folder 5)
  - Life: 1992: Edit, 197239 (Offsite-box 475, Folder 6)
  - Life: 1992: Publishing, 197238 (Offsite-box 475, Folder 7)
  - Life: 1993: Edit, 197237 (Offsite-box 475, Folder 8)
  - Life: 1993: Publishing, 197236 (Offsite-box 475, Folder 9)
  - Life: 1994: Edit, 197235 (Offsite-box 475, Folder 10)
  - Life: 1994: Publishing, 197234 (Offsite-box 475)
  - Life: 1994: Publishing [RESTRICTED], 197233 (Offsite-box R5)
  - Life: 2000: Last Issue, 197232 (Offsite-box 475, Folder 12)
  - Life Group: 2004: Edit &Pub., 197231 (Offsite-box 475, Folder 13)
  - Life International: 1961-1962, 197230 (Offsite-box 475, Folder 14-15)
  - Life International: 1963-1965, 197229 (Offsite-box 475, Folder 16)
  - Life International: 1966-1968, 197228 (Offsite-box 475, Folder 17-18)
  - Life International: 1969 &Later, 197227 (Offsite-box 475, Folder 19-20)
  - Life: Newspaper Supplement: Introduced 2004 [empty], 197226 (Offsite-box 475, Folder 21)
  - Life Spanish: 1961-1965, 197225 (Offsite-box 475, Folder 22-23)
  - Life Spanish: 1966-1970, 197224 (Offsite-box 475, Folder 24)
  - Life Special Reports: 1976-1977, 197223 (Offsite-box 475)
  - Life Special Reports: 1976-1977 [RESTRICTED], 197222 (Offsite-box R5)
  - Little Brown & Co., 197221 (Offsite-box 475, Folder 26-27)
  - Magazine Administrative Services: 1987-, 197220 (Offsite-box 475, Folder 28)
  - Mad Magazine: 1992-, 197219 (Offsite-box 476, Folder 1)
  - Magazine Administrative Services: The Time Inc. Magazine Store, 197218 (Offsite-box 476, Folder 2)
  - Magazine Administrative Services: 1988, 197217 (Offsite-box 476, Folder 3)
  - Magazine Communications, 197216 (Offsite-box 476, Folder 4)
  - Magazine Development: General: 1963-6/1973, 197215 (Offsite-box 476, Folder 5)
  - Magazine Development: General: 7/1973-12/1973, 197214 (Offsite-box 476, Folder 6)
  - Magazine Development: General: 1974, 197213 (Offsite-box 476, Folder 7)
  - Magazine Development: General: 1975-1976, 197212 (Offsite-box 476, Folder 8-9)
  - Magazine Development: General: 1977-1984, 197211 (Offsite-box 476, Folder 10-11)
  - Magazine Development: General: 1985-, 197210 (Offsite-box 476, Folder 12)
  - Magazine Group: 1980-1981: American Renewal, 197209 (Offsite-box 476)
  - Magazine Group: 1980-1981: American Renewal [RESTRICTED], 197208 (Offsite-box R5)
  - Magazine Group: 1981-: Financial & Development Group, 197207 (Offsite-box 476, Folder 14)
  - Magazine Group: 1969-1986: Miscellaneous, 197206 (Offsite-box 476, Folder 15)
  - Magazine Group: 1987-1989: Miscellaneous, 197205 (Offsite-box 476)
  - Magazine Group: 1987-1989: Miscellaneous [RESTRICTED], 197204 (Offsite-box R5)
  - Magazine Group: 1990-, 197203 (Offsite-box 476, Folder 18)
  - Magazine Manufacturing and Distribution: 1987-Oct. 1992, 197202 (Offsite-box 476, Folder 19)
  - Magazine Manufacturing Services, 197201 (Offsite-box 476, Folder 20)
  - Manhattan Cable T.V.: 1965-1972, 197200 (Offsite-box 476)
  - Manhattan Cable T.V.: 1965-1972 [RESTRICTED], 197199 (Offsite-box R5)
  - Manhattan Cable: 1973-1975, 197198 (Offsite-box 477)
  - Manhattan Cable: 1973-1975 [RESTRICTED], 197197 (Offsite-box R5)
  - Manhattan Cable: 1976-1987, 197196 (Offsite-box 477, Folder 3)
  - Manhattan Cable: 1988-, 197195 (Offsite-box 477, Folder 4)
  - March of Time: Movie, 197194 (Offsite-box 477)
  - March of Time: Movie [RESTRICTED], 197193 (Offsite-box R5)
  - March of Time: Movie: 1975 & Later: Possible Broadway Show Adaption, 197192 (Offsite-box 477)
  - March of Time: Movie: 1975 & Later: Possible Broadway Show Adaption [RESTRICTED], 197191 (Offsite-box R5)
  - March of Time: Radio, 197190 (Offsite-box 477, Folder 8)
  - Martha Stewart Living Enterprises, 197189 (Offsite-box 477, Folder 9)
  - Money: 1970 &Before: Origins, 197188 (Offsite-box 477, Folder 10)
  - Money: 1971: Circulation Promotion, 197187 (Offsite-box 477, Folder 11)
  - Money: 1971: Pre-Publication, 197186 (Offsite-box 477, Folder 12)
  - Money: 1971: Prospectus, 197185 (Offsite-box 477, Folder 13)
  - Money: 1972: Edit: Jan.-June, 197184 (Offsite-box 477, Folder 14)
  - Money: 1972: Edit: July-Dec., 197183 (Offsite-box 477, Folder 15)
  - Money: 1972: First Issue, 197182 (Offsite-box 477, Folder 16)
  - Money: 1973: Promotion: Adv. &Circ., 197181 (Offsite-box 477, Folder 17)
  - Money: 1972: Publicity, 197180 (Offsite-box 477, Folder 18)
  - Money: 1972: Publishing: Jan.-March, 197179 (Offsite-box 477)
  - Money: 1972: Publishing: Jan.-March [RESTRICTED], 197178 (Offsite-box R5)
  - Money: 1972: Publishing: April-June, 197177 (Offsite-box 477, Folder 20)
  - Money: 1972: Publishing: July-Sept., 197176 (Offsite-box 477, Folder 21)
  - Money: 1972: Publishing: Oct.-Dec., 197175 (Offsite-box 477, Folder 22)
  - Money: 1973: Edit, 197174 (Offsite-box 477, Folder 23)
  - Money: 1973: Publishing, 197173 (Offsite-box 477, Folder 24)
  - Money: 1974: Edit, 197172 (Offsite-box 477, Folder 25)
  - Money: 1974: Publishing, 197171 (Offsite-box 477, Folder 26)
  - Money: 1975: Board of Directors: Miscellaneous, 197170 (Offsite-box 477, Folder 27)
  - Money: 1975: Edit, 197169 (Offsite-box 477, Folder 28)
  - Money: 1972: Dummies, 197168 (Offsite-box 477, Folder 29)
  - Money: 1975: Publishing, 197167 (Offsite-box 477, Folder 30-31)
  - Money: 1976: Edit [empty], 197166 (Offsite-box 477, Folder 32)
  - Money: 1976: Publishing, 197165 (Offsite-box 477, Folder 33)
  - Money: 1977: Edit, 197164 (Offsite-box 478, Folder 1)
  - Money: 1977: Publishing [empty], 197163 (Offsite-box 478, Folder 2)
  - Money: 1978: Edit, 197162 (Offsite-box 478, Folder 3)
  - Money: 1978: Publishing, 197161 (Offsite-box 478, Folder 4)
  - Money: 1979: Edit, 197160 (Offsite-box 478, Folder 5)
  - Money: 1979: Publishing [empty], 197159 (Offsite-box 478, Folder 6)
  - Money: 1980: Edit, 197158 (Offsite-box 478, Folder 7)
  - Money: 1980: Publishing, 197157 (Offsite-box 478, Folder 8)
  - Money: 1981: Edit, 197156 (Offsite-box 478, Folder 9)
  - Money: 1981: Publishing, 197155 (Offsite-box 478, Folder 10)
  - Money: 1982: Edit, 197154 (Offsite-box 478, Folder 11)
  - Money: 1982: Publishing, 197153 (Offsite-box 478, Folder 12)
  - Money: 1983: Edit, 197152 (Offsite-box 478, Folder 13)
  - Money: 1983: Publishing, 197151 (Offsite-box 478, Folder 14)
  - Money: 1984: Edit, 197150 (Offsite-box 478, Folder 15)
  - Money: 1984: Publishing, 197149 (Offsite-box 478, Folder 16)
  - Money: 1985: Edit: Miscellaneous, 197148 (Offsite-box 478, Folder 17)
  - Money: 1985: Publishing, 197147 (Offsite-box 478, Folder 18)
  - Money: 1986: Edit: Miscellaneous, 197146 (Offsite-box 478, Folder 19)
  - Money: 1986: Publishing, 197145 (Offsite-box 478, Folder 20)
  - Money: 1987: Edit, 197144 (Offsite-box 478, Folder 21)
  - Money: 1987: Publishing, 197143 (Offsite-box 478, Folder 22)
  - Money: 1988: Edit, 197142 (Offsite-box 478, Folder 23)
  - Money: 1988: Publishing, 197141 (Offsite-box 478, Folder 24)
  - Money: 1989: Edit, 197140 (Offsite-box 478, Folder 25)
  - Money: 1989: Publishing, 197139 (Offsite-box 478, Folder 26)
  - Money: 1990: Edit, 197138 (Offsite-box 478, Folder 27)
  - Money: 1990: Publishing, 197137 (Offsite-box 478, Folder 28)
  - Money: 1991: Edit, 197136 (Offsite-box 478, Folder 29)
  - Money: 1991: Publishing, 197135 (Offsite-box 478, Folder 30)
  - Money: 1992: Edit, 197134 (Offsite-box 478, Folder 31)
  - Money: 1992: Publishing, 197133 (Offsite-box 478, Folder 32)
  - Money: 1993: Edit, 197132 (Offsite-box 478, Folder 33)
  - Money: 1993: Publishing, 197131 (Offsite-box 478, Folder 34)
  - Money: 1994: Edit, 197130 (Offsite-box 478, Folder 35)
  - Money: 1994: Publishing, 197129 (Offsite-box 478, Folder 36)
  - Money: 1995: Publishing, 197128 (Offsite-box 478, Folder 37)
  - Money: 1995: Edit, 197127 (Offsite-box 478, Folder 38)
  - Money: 1996: Edit, 197126 (Offsite-box 478, Folder 39)
  - Money: 1996: Publishing, 197125 (Offsite-box 478, Folder 40)
  - Money: 1997: Edit, 197124 (Offsite-box 478, Folder 41)
  - Money: 1997: Publishing, 197123 (Offsite-box 478, Folder 42)
  - Money Japan: 1985-, 197122 (Offsite-box 478, Folder 43)
  - Money: 1997: Your Company [empty], 197121 (Offsite-box 478, Folder 44)
  - Mutual Funds: 1998: Edit &Publishing, 197120 (Offsite-box 478, Folder 45)
  - Newsbureau [empty], 197119 (Offsite-box 478, Folder 46)
  - Money: 1989: Publishing, 197118 (Offsite-box 478, Folder 9)
  - Money: 1990: Edit, 197117 (Offsite-box 478, Folder 10)
  - Money: 1990: Publishing, 197116 (Offsite-box 478, Folder 11)
  - Money: 1991: Edit, 197115 (Offsite-box 478, Folder 12)
  - Money: 1991: Publishing, 197114 (Offsite-box 478, Folder 13)
  - Money: 1992: Edit, 197113 (Offsite-box 478, Folder 14)
  - Newspapers: 1948-1965: Miscellaneous, 197112 (Offsite-box 478, Folder 47)
  - Newspapers: 1966-1967: Miscellaneous, 197111 (Offsite-box 478, Folder 48-49)
  - Newspapers: 1968-1969: Miscellaneous, 197110 (Offsite-box 478, Folder 50)
  - Newspapers: 1970-: Miscellaneous, 197109 (Offsite-box 478, Folder 51)
  - New York Graphic Society Ltd.: 1966-1981, 197108 (Offsite-box 478, Folder 52)
  - Nuts, 197107 (Offsite-box 478, Folder 53)
  - Offices: Chicago, 197106 (Offsite-box 478, Folder 54)
  - Offices: New York, 197105 (Offsite-box 478, Folder 55)
  - Panorama: 1962-1969: Argentina, 197104 (Offsite-box 478)
  - Panorama: 1962-1969: Argentina [RESTRICTED], 197103 (Offsite-box R5)
  - Panorama: Italy: Dummies &First Issue, 197102 (Offsite-box 478, Folder 58-59)
  - Panorama: 1960-1961: Italy, 197101 (Offsite-box 478, Folder 60)
  - Panorama: 1962: Italy, 197100 (Offsite-box 479, Folder 1)
  - Panorama: 1963: Italy, 197099 (Offsite-box 479, Folder 2)
  - Panorama: 1964-1965: Italy, 197098 (Offsite-box 479, Folder 3)
  - Parenting: 1986-1987, 197097 (Offsite-box 479, Folder 4)
  - Parenting: 1988-, 197096 (Offsite-box 479, Folder 5)
  - People: 1973: Dummies (1), 197095 (Offsite-box 479, Folder 6)
  - People: 1973: Dummies (2), 197094 (Offsite-box 479, Folder 7)
  - People: 1973: Dummies (3), 197093 (Offsite-box 479, Folder 8-9)
  - People: 1973: Dummies (4), 197092 (Offsite-box 479, Folder 10)
  - People: 1973 &Before: Origins, 197091 (Offsite-box 479, Folder 11)
  - People: 1973: Pre-Publication: Edit, 197090 (Offsite-box 479, Folder 12)
  - People: 1973: Pre-Publication: Edit: Comment, 197089 (Offsite-box 479, Folder 13)
  - People: 1973: Pre-Publication: Publishing: May-July, 197088 (Offsite-box 479, Folder 14)
  - People: 1973: Pre-Publication: Publishing: Aug.-Oct., 197087 (Offsite-box 479, Folder 15-16)
  - People: 1973: Pre-Publication: Publishing: Nov.-Dec., 197086 (Offsite-box 479, Folder 17)
  - People: 1973: Prospectus, 197085 (Offsite-box 479, Folder 18)
  - People: 1973: Publicity, 197084 (Offsite-box 479, Folder 19)
  - People: 3/4/1974: First Issue, 197083 (Offsite-box 479, Folder 20)
  - People: 1974: Edit: Jan.-June, 197082 (Offsite-box 479, Folder 21)
  - People: 1974: July-Dec., 197081 (Offsite-box 479, Folder 22)
  - People: 1974: Publicity, 197080 (Offsite-box 479, Folder 23)
  - People: 1974: Publishing: Jan.-March, 197079 (Offsite-box 480)
  - People: 1974: Publishing: Jan.-March [RESTRICTED], 197078 (Offsite-box R5)
  - People: 1974: Publishing: April-June, 197077 (Offsite-box 480, Folder 2)
  - People: 1974: Publishing: July-Sept., 197076 (Offsite-box 480, Folder 3)
  - People: 1975: Edit, 197075 (Offsite-box 480, Folder 5)
  - People: 1975: Publishing, 197074 (Offsite-box 480, Folder 6)
  - People: 1976: Edit, 197073 (Offsite-box 480, Folder 7)
  - People: 1976: Publishing, 197072 (Offsite-box 480, Folder 8)
  - People: 1977: Edit, 197071 (Offsite-box 480, Folder 9)
  - People: 1977: Publishing, 197070 (Offsite-box 480, Folder 10)
  - People: 1978: Edit, 197069 (Offsite-box 480, Folder 11)
  - People: 1978: Publishing, 197068 (Offsite-box 480, Folder 12)
  - People: 1979: Edit, 197067 (Offsite-box 480, Folder 13)
  - People: 1979: Publishing, 197066 (Offsite-box 480, Folder 14)
  - People: 1980: Edit: Miscellaneous, 197065 (Offsite-box 480, Folder 15)
  - People: 1980: Publishing, 197064 (Offsite-box 480)
  - People: 1980: Publishing [RESTRICTED], 197063 (Offsite-box R5)
  - People: 1981: Edit: Miscellaneous, 197062 (Offsite-box 480, Folder 17)
  - People: 1981: Publishing, 197061 (Offsite-box 480, Folder 18)
  - People: 1982: Edit, 197060 (Offsite-box 480, Folder 19)
  - People: 1982: Publishing, 197059 (Offsite-box 480)
  - People: 1982: Publishing [RESTRICTED], 197058 (Offsite-box R5)
  - People: 1983: Edit, 197057 (Offsite-box 480, Folder 21)
  - People: 1983: Publishing, 197056 (Offsite-box 480, Folder 22-23)
  - People: 1984: Edit: Miscellaneous, 197055 (Offsite-box 480, Folder 24)
  - People: 1984: 10th Anniversary Issue, 197054 (Offsite-box 480, Folder 25)
  - People: 1984: Publishing, 197053 (Offsite-box 480, Folder 26)
  - People: 1986: Publishing, 197052 (Offsite-box 480, Folder 27)
  - People: 1986: Edit, 197051 (Offsite-box 480, Folder 28)
  - People: 1986: Publishing, 197050 (Offsite-box 480, Folder 29)
  - People: 1987: Edit, 197049 (Offsite-box 480, Folder 30)
  - People: 1987: Publishing, 197048 (Offsite-box 480, Folder 31)
  - People: 1988: Edit, 197047 (Offsite-box 480, Folder 32)
  - People: 1988: Publishing, 197046 (Offsite-box 480, Folder 33)
  - People: 1989: Edit, 197045 (Offsite-box 480, Folder 34)
  - People: 1989: Publishing, 197044 (Offsite-box 480, Folder 35)
  - People: 1990: Edit, 197043 (Offsite-box 480, Folder 36)
  - People: 1990: Publishing, 197042 (Offsite-box 480, Folder 37)
  - People: 1991: Edit, 197041 (Offsite-box 480, Folder 38)
  - People: 1991: Publishing, 197040 (Offsite-box 480, Folder 39)
  - People: 1992: Edit, 197039 (Offsite-box 480, Folder 40)
  - People: 1992: Publishing, 197038 (Offsite-box 480, Folder 41)
  - People: 1993: Edit, 197037 (Offsite-box 480, Folder 42)
  - People: 1994: Edit, 197036 (Offsite-box 480, Folder 44)
  - People: 1994: Publishing, 197035 (Offsite-box 480, Folder 45)
  - People: 1994: 20th Anniversary, 197034 (Offsite-box 480, Folder 46)
  - People: 1995: Edit [empty], 197033 (Offsite-box 480, Folder 47)
  - People: 1995-1996: Publishing, 197032 (Offsite-box 480, Folder 48)
  - People: 1997-1999: Edit, 197031 (Offsite-box 480, Folder 49)
  - People: 1997-1998: Publishing, 197030 (Offsite-box 480, Folder 50)
  - People: 2000: Edit, 197029 (Offsite-box 480, Folder 51)
  - People: 2004: Edit: 30th Anniversary, 197028 (Offsite-box 480, Folder 52)
  - People: 2001-: Publishing, 197027 (Offsite-box 480, Folder 53)
  - People en Espanol: 1997-: Edit, 197026 (Offsite-box 480, Folder 54)
  - People en Espanol: 1997-: Publishing, 197025 (Offsite-box 480, Folder 55)
  - People Group: 1998-, 197024 (Offsite-box 480, Folder 56)
  - People International: 1991-: Who Weekly, 197023 (Offsite-box 480, Folder 57)
  - People Style Watch: February 2007: First Issue, 197022 (Offsite-box 480, Folder 58)
  - Personnel & Organization: Minorities: 1961-1964, 197021 (Offsite-box 480, Folder 58)
  - Personnel & Organization: Minorities: 1965-1970, 197020 (Offsite-box 480, Folder 60)
  - Personnel & Organization: Minorities: 1971-1975, 197019 (Offsite-box 480-481)
  - Personnel & Organization: Minorities: 1976 & Later, 197018 (Offsite-box 481, Folder 2-3)
  - Personnel & Organization: Out @ Time-Inc, 197017 (Offsite-box 481, Folder 4)
  - Personnel & Organization: Outside Activity: 1961-1964, 197016 (Offsite-box 481, Folder 5)
  - Personnel & Organization: Outside Activity: 1965-1970, 197015 (Offsite-box 481, Folder 6)
  - Personnel & Organization: Outside Activity: 1971-1975, 197014 (Offsite-box 481, Folder 7)
  - Personnel & Organization: Outside Activity: 1976 & Later, 197013 (Offsite-box 481, Folder 8)
  - Personnel & Organization: Strike: Jan.-May 1976, 197012 (Offsite-box 481, Folder 9-11)
  - Personnel & Organization: Strike: June-Dec. 1976, 197011 (Offsite-box 481)
  - Personnel & Organization: Strike: June-Dec. 1976 [RESTRICTED], 197010 (Offsite-box R5)
  - Personnel & Organization: Women: 1961-1969, 197009 (Offsite-box 481, Folder 14)
  - Personnel & Organization: Women: 1970: Jan.-May, 197008 (Offsite-box 481, Folder 15)
  - Personnel & Organization: Women: 1970: June, 197007 (Offsite-box 481, Folder 16)
  - Personnel & Organization: Women: 1970: July-Aug., 197006 (Offsite-box 481, Folder 17)
  - Personnel & Organization: 1970: Sept.-Dec., 197005 (Offsite-box 481, Folder 18)
  - Personnel & Organization: Women: 1971, 197004 (Offsite-box 481)
  - Personnel & Organization: Women: 1971 [RESTRICTED], 197003 (Offsite-box R5)
  - Personnel & Organization: Women: 1972, 197002 (Offsite-box 481, Folder 20)
  - Personnel & Organization: Women: 1973, 197001 (Offsite-box 481, Folder 21)
  - Personnel & Organization: Women: 1974 & Later, 197000 (Offsite-box 481, Folder 22)
  - Personnel & Organization: Miscellaneous: 1961, 196999 (Offsite-box 481, Folder 23)
  - Personnel & Organization: Miscellaneous: 1962, 196998 (Offsite-box 481, Folder 24)
  - Personnel & Organization: Miscellaneous: 1963, 196997 (Offsite-box 481, Folder 25)
  - Personnel & Organization: Miscellaneous: 1964, 196996 (Offsite-box 481, Folder 26)
  - Personnel & Organization: Miscellaneous: 1965, 196995 (Offsite-box 482, Folder 1)
  - Personnel & Organization: Miscellaneous: 1966, 196994 (Offsite-box 482, Folder 2)
  - Personnel & Organization: Miscellaneous: 1967, 196993 (Offsite-box 482, Folder 3)
  - Personnel & Organization: Miscellaneous: 1968, 196992 (Offsite-box 482, Folder 4)
  - Personnel & Organization: Miscellaneous: 1969, 196991 (Offsite-box 482, Folder 5)
  - Personnel & Organization: Miscellaneous: 1970, 196990 (Offsite-box 482, Folder 6)
  - Personnel & Organization: Miscellaneous: 1971, 196989 (Offsite-box 482, Folder 7)
  - Personnel & Organization: Miscellaneous: 1972, 196988 (Offsite-box 482, Folder 8)
  - Personnel & Organization: Miscellaneous: 1973, 196987 (Offsite-box 482, Folder 9)
  - Personnel & Organization: Miscellaneous: 1974, 196986 (Offsite-box 482, Folder 10)
  - Personnel & Organization: Miscellaneous: 1975, 196985 (Offsite-box 482, Folder 11)
  - Personnel & Organization: Miscellaneous: 1976, 196984 (Offsite-box 482, Folder 12)
  - Personnel & Organization: Miscellaneous: 1977, 196983 (Offsite-box 482, Folder 13)
  - Personnel & Organization: Miscellaneous: 1978, 196982 (Offsite-box 482, Folder 14)
  - Personnel & Organization: Miscellaneous: 1979, 196981 (Offsite-box 482, Folder 15)
  - Personnel & Organization: Miscellaneous: 1980, 196980 (Offsite-box 482, Folder 16)
  - Personnel & Organization: Miscellaneous: 1981, 196979 (Offsite-box 482, Folder 17)
  - Personnel & Organization: Miscellaneous: 1982, 196978 (Offsite-box 482, Folder 18)
  - Personnel & Organization: Miscellaneous: 1983, 196977 (Offsite-box 482, Folder 19)
  - Personnel & Organization: Miscellaneous: 1984, 196976 (Offsite-box 482, Folder 20)
  - Personnel & Organization: Miscellaneous: 1985, 196975 (Offsite-box 482, Folder 21)
  - Personnel & Organization: Miscellaneous: 1986, 196974 (Offsite-box 482, Folder 22)
  - Personnel & Organization: Miscellaneous: 1987, 196973 (Offsite-box 482)
  - Personnel & Organization: Miscellaneous: 1987 [RESTRICTED], 196972 (Offsite-box R5)
  - Personnel & Organization: Miscellaneous: 1988, 196971 (Offsite-box 482, Folder 24)
  - Personnel & Organization: Miscellaneous: 1989, 196970 (Offsite-box 482, Folder 25)
  - Personnel & Organization: Miscellaneous: 1990, 196969 (Offsite-box 482, Folder 26)
  - Personnel & Organization: Miscellaneous: 1991, 196968 (Offsite-box 483, Folder 1)
  - Personnel & Organization: Miscellaneous: 1992, 196967 (Offsite-box 483, Folder 2)
  - Personnel & Organization: Miscellaneous: 1993, 196966 (Offsite-box 483, Folder 3)
  - Personnel & Organization: Miscellaneous: 1994, 196965 (Offsite-box 483, Folder 4)
  - Personnel & Organization: Miscellaneous: 1995-, 196964 (Offsite-box 483, Folder 5)
  - Pioneer Press: 1968-1969: Miscellaneous, 196963 (Offsite-box 483)
  - Pioneer Press: 1968-1969: Miscellaneous [RESTRICTED], 196962 (Offsite-box R5)
  - Pioneer Press: 1969: Hollister Publishing, 196961 (Offsite-box 483)
  - Pioneer Press: 1969: Hollister Publishing [RESTRICTED], 196960 (Offsite-box R5)
  - Pioneer Press: 1970: Miscellaneous, 196959 (Offsite-box 483)
  - Pioneer Press: 1970: Miscellaneous [RESTRICTED], 196958 (Offsite-box R5)
  - Pioneer Press: 1971 & Later: Miscellaneous, 196957 (Offsite-box 483, Folder 10)
  - Pioneer Press: 1970-1971: Pickwick Papers, 196956 (Offsite-box 483)
  - Pioneer Press: 1970-1971: Pickwick Papers [RESTRICTED], 196955 (Offsite-box R5)
  - Popular Science: Edit, 196954 (Offsite-box 483, Folder 12)
  - President ( Fortune International): 1961: Pre-Publication, 196953 (Offsite-box 483, Folder 13)
  - President ( Fortune International): 1962: Pre-Publication (1), 196952 (Offsite-box 483, Folder 14)
  - President ( Fortune International): 1962: Pre-Publication (2), 196951 (Offsite-box 483)
  - President ( Fortune International): 1962: Pre-Publication (2) [RESTRICTED], 196950 (Offsite-box R5)